# **ANNA FUNSTEN**

# **Data Scientist and Analyst**

Washington, DC | alfunsten@gmail.com | 301-580-9175

#### **SUMMARY**

Creative and insightful data analyst with enthusiasm for research and public health. Trained and practiced as a pediatric nurse practitioner with a deep knowledge in disease processes and strong communication skills with patients and co-workers. Natural intuition to interpret, problem solve and visualize data.

## **SKILLS**

- **PROGRAMING LANGUAGES**: Python, Numpy, Pandas, and Sklearn, knowledge of SQL, Pytest, Spark, C++, SPSS, and R
- · **MACHINE LEARNING**: regression, classification, clustering, feature engineering, NLP, bayesian statistics, forecasting, PCA, recommender systems, neural networks
- · DATA VISUALIZATION: Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly, knowledge of Tableau
- · EMR: eClinicalWorks, Greenway Health EHR and Epic EMR

# **EXPERIENCE**

# GENERAL ASSEMBLY Data Science Immersive

WASHINGTON, DC March 2021 - June 2021

- Acquired extensive data cleaning, analysis, programming and machine learning skills through 40 hour week classes and 20+ hours of assignments outside of class
- · Accurately completed 19 data driven labs and 5 projects addressing solutions to machine learning research questions
- · Successfully presented engaging data driven analysis of projects to cohort
- Excelled in a final capstone project that used a neural network image classification model to successfully identify ear infection images from not infected eardrum images

# MCKNIGHT PEDIATRICS Advanced Practice Nurse

WASHINGTON, DC Aug 2020 - Feb 2021

- Managed 15-20 personalized care plans for sick and well children ages 0-21 with comprehensive evaluations
- Performed thorough well child exam for newborns, school physicals, sport physicals and pre-operative evaluations that included a physical assessment, medication management and preventive healthcare guidance.
- Conducted telehealth medical consultation for children daily
- Diagnosed, managed and educated children and families in regard to the COVID-19 pandemic

# HINSDALE PEDIATRIC ASSOCIATES

#### **Advanced Practice Nurse**

CHICAGO, IL March 2019 - March 2020

- · Cared for 25+ sick patient encounters a day with precise diagnostic skills
- · Actively individualized care plans for each client by acknowledging past medical history and chronic conditions
- · Readily followed up with ill children and abnormal lab results through subsequent visit or telephone encounter
- · Provided families with supplemental reading containing information on anticipatory guidance/disease management
- Completed thorough charts of patient encounters within 24 hours of visit

#### LINCOLN PEDIATRIC CENTER

#### **Advanced Practice Nurse**

CHICAGO, IL Oct 2017 - March 2019

- · Independently managed pediatric center when main physician is not present through patient encounters, patient consultation calls, and scheduling appointments
- Efficiently worked in a busy pediatric clinic seeing on average 4 patients an hour
- · Oriented, mentored, precepted, and reviewed medical students
- · Managed children with chronic or complex illnesses while collaborating with specialty providers

# UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN HEALTH SYSTEM Strong Military Families, Research Assistant

ANN ARBOR, MI May 2014 – Aug 2015

- · Administered and documented baseline and post study behavior
- · Improved child behavior through relationship development and implementation of activities designed by the child team leader
- · Tabulated, standardized, and analyzed data using SPSS and Excel to isolate effectiveness of the program

#### **EDUCATION**

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Data Science Immersive

WASHINGTON, DC

March 2021 - June 2021

VANDERBILT UNIVERSITY

MSN-Pediatric Nurse Practitioner-Primary Care

NASHVILLE, TN

Aug 2015 - Aug 2017

UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN
College of Literature, Science, and the Arts
BS in Biopsychology, Cognition, and Neuroscience
with a minor in Applied Statistics

ANN ARBOR, MI Sept 2011 - May 2015

## **LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS**

### **Advanced Practice Nurse and Registered Professional Nurse**

Maryland Board of Nursing DC Board of Nursing Virginia Board of Nursing

## Certified Pediatric Nurse Practitioner- Primary Care (CPNP-PC)

Pediatric Nursing Certification Board

# **Pediatric Advanced Life Support**

American Heart Association

## **Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers**

American Heart Association